Blurt! is a family, comedy, tv movie film directed by Michelle Johnston.
When nice-guy Jeremy Martin puts on mysterious virtual reality glasses at the mall, he
suddenly loses his “inside voice” and starts spouting every thought he has out loud.
Making matters worse, Jeremy is running for student council president against his
classmate Milly, who is full of great ideas to improve the school.
Desperate to get back to normal, Jeremy and his sister Victoria must figure
out how to convince his brain that he can speak up for himself.
Jeremy Martin, played by Jace Norman.
Victoria Martin, played by Joelle Siwa.
Spanish Teacher, played by Cynthia Mendez.
Milley, played by Daniella Taylor.
Lead Dancer, played by Taylor Dianne Robinson.
Mrs. McCann, played by Aliza Vellani.
Truth or Dare, also known as Blumhouse's Truth or Dare, is a 2018 American supernatural horror film directed
and co-written (alongside Michael Reisz, Jillian Jacobs, and Chris Roach) by Jeff Wadlow.
The film stars Lucy Hale, Tyler Posey, Violett Beane, Hayden Szeto, Sophia Taylor Ali, and Landon Liboiron as a group of college students who play a game of
truth or dare while on vacation in Mexico, only to realize it has deadly consequences if they do not follow through on their obligations.
Jason Blum produced through his Blumhouse Productions banner,
and Universal Pictures distributed the film.
Released in theaters on Friday, April 13, 2018, the film received mostly negative reviews from critics, who said it was "neither inventive nor scary enough to set itself apart from
the decades of dreary slashers that came before it." The film was a box office success, grossing $95 million worldwide against its $3.5 million production budget.
The film explores themes of high school, virtual
reality, school, election, family.
The tone is lighthearted.